Guide to the Cindy Domingo Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Cindy Domingo papers, 1973-2009; 5651-003; 16 cubic feet 16 boxes
  - CINDY DOMINGO PAPERS, SERIES I (Box-folder Box 1-Box 16)
    - Guerrero, Amado. Philippine Society and Revolution. 3rd ed. Oakland: International Association of Filipino, 1979. Print. (Box-folder 3/40)
    - Guerrero, Amado. Specific Characterstics of People's War. Oakland: International Association of Filipino, 1979. Print. (Box-folder 3/41)
    - Sister Cities: Cuba, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - MIscellaneous Personal Files, 2001-2009 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - MIscellaneous Personal Files (2), 2000-2003 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Caughlan, John, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - International Worker to Worker Project, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Cuba, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Originals: National Asian Pacific American Women Forum (NAPAWF), 2003-2006 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Clippings: MLK Day, 2003-2010 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Incite conference - New Orleans 2005 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Building On Beijing, 1997 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - "Women and the Media Delegation to Cuba", 2000 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Pamphlets, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Miscellaneous Information, 1985-2010 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF), 2000-2005 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - WILPF National Board Packet, 2005 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Filipino Community, 1979-1992 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Taliba, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - WILPF Cuba Action Team, 1998-2010 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - WILPF Cuba Action Team 2, 2000 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Miscellanous: WILPF, 2002-2010 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Human Trafficking, 2002 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Tax System- WA state, 2004 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Report to the Governor on Discrimination Against Asians, 1973 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Health Assessment of Elderly Filipinos in International District, 1972 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Northwest Social Forum Planning Retreat, 2004 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Katipunan, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Katipunan (2), 1975-1991 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - Katipunan (3), 1975-1983 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Katipunan (4), 1975-1980 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Event Information: Cuba, 2002 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Pacific Ecumenical Forum, 1992 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Misc. News Clippings Part 1 of 2, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Misc. News Clippings Part 2 of 2, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Silme Domingo Memorial/Apartment Naming, 1988-2003 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Race and Gender Relations in U.S. and Cuba Part 1 of 2, 2000-2010 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Race and Gender Relations in U.S. and Cuba Part 2 of 2, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Marxist-Leninist Journal of Rectification, 1981 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom Newsletter, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Women's Progress since 1959, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - US Woman/Cuba Collaboration, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Woman and Cuba Collaboration, 2002 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Larry Gossett Literature, Undated (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Larry Gossett/Issues, 1993 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - By-Laws/National Rainbow Coalition, 1989 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - By-Laws/Washington State, 1989 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Operational Procedures for Washington State Rainbow Coalition, 1989 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - A Mind Is A Terrible Thing To Waste/Brisker Part 1 of 2, 1986 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - A Mind Is A Terrible Thing To Waste/Brisker Part 2 of 2, 1986 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Larry Gossett/Letters to Seattle City Council, 1989 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Larry Gossett Campaign Committee, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Gossett Campaign Plan Notebook, 1993 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Larry Gossett Campaign Misc., 1993 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Larry Gossett Campaign, 1993 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Larry Gossett Fundraising Committee, 1993 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Two Cloth Banners, Undated (Box-folder Box 5)
    - Cuban-U.S. relations, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Commission for assistance to a free cuba [CAFC], 2004 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Everywoman's movement for cuba, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Miscellaneous personal papers part 1 of 2, 1993-2010 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Miscellaneous personal papers part 1 of 2, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1994-2003 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Cuban periodicals part 1 of 2, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Cuban periodicals part 2 of 2, 2003-2010 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Misc. periodicals part 1 of 2, 1992-2002 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Misc. periodicals part 2 of 2, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Workers in cuba by evenson, Undated (Box-folder 6/11)
    - US women's movement-cuba relations part 1 of 2, 2000-2011 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - US women's movement-cuba relations part 2 of 2, 2002-2011 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - Asian pacific american labor alliance [APALA] part 1 of 3, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Asian pacific american labor alliance [APALA] part 2 of 3, 1997-2010 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - Asian pacific american labor alliance [APALA] part 3 of 3, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - Aurora project, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 6/17)
    - Alaskero script, 2003 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - Amigo-the movie, 2011 (Box-folder 6/19)
    - Association for women's rights [AWID], 2004 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - Platform for action, 2005 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - Casey Foundation Leadership, 2005 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - Convention on discrimination against women, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - Bayan statement on silme and gene, 2008 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Leslie lum discrimination case, 2008 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Wilson chin for seattle school board, 2009 (Box-folder 6/26)
    - Carlos Bulosan Symposium, 2006 (Box-folder 6/27)
    - Yellow Banner, Undated (Box-folder Box 6)
    - Research Files: Cuba Papers Part 1 of 4, 2001-2007 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Research Files: Cuba Papers Part 2 of 4, 2001-2009 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Research Files: Cuba Papers Part 3 of 4, 2000-2010 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Research Files: Cuba Correspondence/Papers Part 4 of 4, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Research Files: U.S. Women and Cuba Collaboration, 2003 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF) Part 1 of 2, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF) Part 2 of 2, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom-Misc. Emails, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty review Conference, 2010 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - U.W. Women and Cuba Collaboration, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Research Files: Cuba Trip Details, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Research Files: Informational Cuba Event Flyers, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Research Files: Miscellaneous Collaboration Papers, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Research Files: Thomas McKeown, Meet Fidel Castro, 2008 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Research Files: Mailing List/Cuba Collaboration, 2004 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Research Files: Webpage U.S. Women/Cuba, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Research Files: Cuba Information, 2003-2009 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Rank and File Committee Election Slate, 1978 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - The Invisible Workforce: Women in the Informal Economy, 2000 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Addressing Informality, Reducing Poverty: A Policy Response to the Informal Economy, 2001 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Newsletter in Coordination With the Pacific Women's Resources: The Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes UPDATE, 1981 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Northwest Asian American theater 20th Anniversary: Dreams and Promises, 1993 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - International Examiner Notes, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - First Biennial Convention of The Japanese American Citizens' League, 1930 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - Transcript of Martin Luther King's "Beyond Vietnam-A Time to Break Silence", 2005 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - Copy of E. San Juan Jr.'s "One Hundred Years of Producing and reproducing the 'Filipino'", Undated (Box-folder 8/9)
    - Pilipino People's Far West Convention, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Women Makes Movies Magazine, 2006 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Jack C. Buenavista Funeral, 1996 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Collective Voices Newspaper Vol.1 Issue 1, Undated (Box-folder 8/13)
    - ifco NEWS, 1998 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Grassroots Global Justice Pamphlet, Undated (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Invitation to KDP 10th Anniversary, 1983 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - Organic Fruit and Vegetable Growing as a National Policy: The Cuban Story; Part 1 of 2, 2006 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom; Part 2 of 2, 2006 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - LELO: Domingio, Viernes, Jefferson Awards Dinner, 2006 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Real Change Newsletter, 2010 (Box-folder 8/20)
    - As the South Goes Newsletter, 2010 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Peace & Freedom Magazine, 2010 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - 1987-2011 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Madre Magazine, Undated (Box-folder 8/24)
    - LaRouche PAC: Act Now to Stop Obama's Nazi Health Plan!, 2009 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Seattle Women Magazine, 2009 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - Brenda Joyce Gossett Wigfall Funeral, 2010 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - LELO's International Worker-to-Worker Project: Brazil Report-Back, 2002 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum & SEIU notes, 1997 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - SEIU Retreat Agenda; Refugee Women Leadership Training; NAPAWF; Part 1 of 2, 1997 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum (NAPAWF), 1997 (Box-folder 8/31)
    - Sisters in Struggle-Sisters In Victory!: Commemorative edition in honor of Silme Domingo and gene Viernes, Mila de Guzman, 2011 (Box-folder 8/32)
    - Civil Rights Issues Facing Asian Americans in the 1990s, 1992 (Box-folder 8/33)
    - Labor4Jusitice: An Open Letter to Activists Concerning Racism in the Anti-War, 2003 (Box-folder 8/34)
    - International Socialist Review: Leonard Peltier and the Indian Struggle for Freedom, 2009 (Box-folder 8/35)
    - LELO: A Driver's License is a Racial Justice Issue, Undated (Box-folder 8/36)
    - AlterNET: How Obama Lost His Voice, and How He Can Get It Back; and Cuba Filers, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 8/37)
    - US Social Forum (USSF), 2010 (Box-folder 8/38)
    - US Social Forum (USSF), 2010 (Box-folder 8/39)
    - MLK Human Rights Conference: Whatcom Social Forum, 2011 (Box-folder 8/40)
    - Pacific Island Voices, 2010 (Box-folder 8/41)
    - Katipunan/National Newspaper of the Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Part 1 of 2, 1982 (Box-folder 8/42)
    - Katipunan/National Newspaper of the Union of Democratic Filipinos (KDP) Part 2 of 2, 1982 (Box-folder 8/43)
    - Katipunan/ Misc. Filipino Newspapers Part 1 of 2, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 8/44)
    - Katipunan/Misc. Filipino Newspapers Part 2 of 2, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 8/45)
    - Katipunan Newspaper/Aquinos Part 1 of 2, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 8/46)
    - Katipunan Newspaper/Cory Part 2 of 2, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 8/47)
    - Katipunan Newspaper/Marcos/Rebellion Part 1 of 2, 1974-1990 (Box-folder 8/48)
    - Katipunan Newspaper/Marcos/Rebellion Part 2 of 2, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 8/49)
    - Katipunan Newspaper/ Fall of Marcos Regime Part 1 of 2, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 8/50)
    - Katipunan Newspaper/ Fall of Marcos Regime Part 2 of 2, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 8/51)
    - Katipunan Newspaper/Misc. Papers Part 1 of 2, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 8/52)
    - Katipunan Newspaper/Misc. Papers Part 2 of 2, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 8/53)
    - First National Conference-San Francisco, CA, 1980 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Alaskero News, Rank and File Committee, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Newspaper Clippings of Marcos Part 1 of 3 -Extradition, 1982 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Newspaper Clippings of Marcos Part 2 of 3 -Extradition, Misc., Articles on the Phillippines, 1982 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Newspaper Clippings of Marcos Part 3 of 3 -Articles on the Phillippines, 1982 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship-Philippine Solidarity Network (CAMD/PSN) Press Release, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Community Newspapers, 1980 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Press Release: Marcos-Aquino, 1986 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - National Democracy and Socialism Part 1 of 2, Undated (Box-folder 9/9)
    - National Democracy and Socialism-Press Release Part 2 of 2, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Articles on the Philippines and Marcos, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Newspaper Clippings and Articles: B. Aquino, Marcos, Protest, 1984 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Philippine National Day: Barrio Fiesta, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Community Newspaper: Kalayaan International Part 1 of 2, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Community Newspaper[?: Kalayaan International Part 2 of 2?], 1974-1976 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Tambulj, Democratic Filipino Newspaper, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Verdict on Aquino Trial, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Filipino Democratic Newspaper, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Philippine Revolution Magazine, 1969 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Emails Regarding Cuban Justice Part 1 of 3, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Emails Regarding Cuban-US relations Part 2 of 3, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Emails/News Clippings Regarding Cuban-US Relations Part 3 of 3, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - "Regret to Inform" Vietnam movie flyers/Domingo Introduction, 2003 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - International Womens Day 2004 Photos, News (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Asian Pacific American Community Summit [APA], 2004 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Emails/News Clippings Supporting Democracy in Venezuela, 2004 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Articles on U.S. Marcos/Filipino Democracy, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Obituaries/Business News, 1982 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Newspaper Clippings of Romero Case/Marcos, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Eastern Economy Magazines Part 1 of 2, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Eastern Economy Magazines Part 2 of 2, 1985 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Filipino Newspaper/Periodicals, 1985 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Philippine Review, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - National Report: Philippines, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Anti-Marcos News Clippings, Undated (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Petition to Free Mila Aguilar, 1985 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - U.S.-Phillippine Relations in Reagan Era, 1982 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Marcos News Clippings Part 1 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Marcos News Clippings Part 2 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Marcos News Clippings Part 3 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Letter to Marcos/ Boy Morales, 1982 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - General Amnesty, Undated (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Extradition Letter, 1982 (Box-folder 10/17)
    - Philippines-MISC, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - National Democratic Alternative [NAT DEM], 1980-1981 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Nationalist Alliance, 1983 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Marcos Visit 1982, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 10/21)
    - Philippine Labor Movement, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - Pinguel, Baitazar Detainee, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - Labor Slideshow Scripts, Undated (Box-folder 10/24)
    - Taguiwalo, Judy Detainee, 1984 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - 1984 Carolling Campaign, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 10/26)
    - Studies, 1984 (Box-folder 10/27)
    - First Regional Congress of Seattle, 1975 (Box-folder 10/28)
    - Filipino Newspaper Clippings, 1981 (Box-folder 10/29)
    - H-1 Nurses Campaign, 1981 (Box-folder 10/30)
    - Slide Show Notes/Philippines, Undated (Box-folder 10/31)
    - 10 Year Anniversary Union of Democratic Filipinos [KDP], 1983 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Filipino Community of Seattle Letters, 1980 (Box-folder 10/33)
    - National Council Report, 1983 (Box-folder 10/34)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos [KDP], 1983-1985 (Box-folder 10/35)
    - Union of Democratic Filipinos [KDP], 1977-1980 (Box-folder 10/36)
    - Misc. Filipino News Clippings, 1973-1985 (Box-folder 10/37)
    - Signed Petition to free Political Prisoners, 1985 (Box-folder 10/38)
    - Notes and Clippings on Comfort Women, 2007 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - World March of Women, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Domestic and Third World Women Rights Part 1 of 2, 1993-2011 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Domestic and Third World Women Rights Part 2 of 2, 2002-2011 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Peace and Freedom Magazine, 2007 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Development of Water Cure by U.S. Military during the Philippines American War, 2008- (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Lt. Ehren K. Watada Campaign, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Hugo Chavez and Venezuela, 2004-2008 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - United States Social Forum Part 1 of 3, 2010 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - United States Social Forum Part 2 of 3, 2010 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - United States Social Forum Part 3 of 3, 2010 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Resist the Empire Newspaper, Undated (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Assassinations, Disappearances, and other Forms of State Terrorism Against Political Activists, 1999-2008 (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Newspapers and Articles on Women's rights, 2005-2010 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - SisterSong-Loretta Ross Event, 2006 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Women Reproductive Health Rights, 2005 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Emails: Peaceful and Credible Elections (COMPACT) Project and Active Citizenship Foundation (ACF), 2010 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Newspaper Clipping: "White Grievance That's Justified", 2010 (Box-folder 11/19)
    - COLORS NW Magazine Clippings, 2007 (Box-folder 11/20)
    - Barack Obama 2008 Election and Campaign Part 1 of 2, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 11/21)
    - Barack Obama 2008 Election and Campaign Part 2 of 2, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 11/22)
    - Using International Human Rights Strategies to Advance Women's Equality, Undated (Box-folder 11/23)
    - Center for Social Justice: Northwest Social Forum, 2004 (Box-folder 11/24)
    - Venezuela Constitution and Visit, 2010 (Box-folder 11/25)
    - Murder in Seattle Manuscript, 1994 (Box-folder 11/26)
    - Floppy Disc, 1992 (Box-folder 11/27)
    - Open Hand Publishing and Funeral Programs, 1994-2011 (Box-folder 11/28)
    - "Turning Grief into Revolutionary Courage" Banner, 1981 (Box-folder 11/29)
    - International Women's Day March and Celebration Poster, 2010 (Box-folder 11/30)
    - "The Coup in the Philippines" Invintation, 1989 (Box-folder 11/31)
    - Misc. News Clippings/ Filipino Exploitation, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Washington Population Studies Part 1 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Washington Population Studies Part 2 of 2, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Issues Impacting Washington State's Asian Pacific American in the 1980's, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - State Steering Committee, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Washington State Rainbow Coalition Retreat, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Jesse Jackson Speech, Undated (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Rainbow Newsletter, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - The Rainbow Report, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Newsletter Congressional Districts, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Membership Committee Minutes, Undated (Box-folder 12/11)
    - National Rainbow Coalition Board of Director Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Membership Committee Membership Lists Part 1 of 2, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Membership Committee Membership Lists Part 2 of 2, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Membership Committee Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 12/15)
    - El Centro de la Raza, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12/16)
    - WSRC Formal Leadership Personal Information, 1990 (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Correspondence National Rainbow Coalition, 1990 (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Convention-Washington State Part 1 of 2, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12/19)
    - Convention-Washington State Part 2 of 2, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Convention-Washington State-1992 (Box-folder 12/21)
    - Rainbow Coalition-Jesse Jackson, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 12/22)
    - Institute for Global Security Studies Part 1 of 3, 1993 (Box-folder 12/23)
    - Institute for Global Security Studies Part 2 of 3, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 12/24)
    - Institute for Global Security Studies Part 3 of 3, 1993 (Box-folder 12/25)
    - Institute for Global Security-U.S.-Philippine Relations, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 12/26)
    - Mailing Lists Part 1 of 2, 1993 (Box-folder 12/27)
    - Mailing Lists Part 2 of 2, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12/28)
    - Larry Gossett Campaign-Campaign Endorsers, 1993 (Box-folder 12/29)
    - Gossett Campaign Donors, 1993 (Box-folder 12/30)
    - Gossett- Letters of Support, 1989 (Box-folder 12/31)
    - Gossett-Misc. Campaign, 1993 (Box-folder 12/32)
    - National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 12/33)
    - Brisker, E.J., Undated- (Box-folder 12/34)
    - Native American Consultation 11/92, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 12/35)
    - Martin Luther King, 1993 (Box-folder 12/36)
    - McClintock, Jessica Issue, 1992 (Box-folder 12/37)
    - Audio Tapes, Undated (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Specific characteristics of people's war in the Philippines, 1979 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - The Coming of the strangers, 1974 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Report of an Amnesty International Mission to the Republic of the Philippines, 1977 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Conditions of the Filipino people under martial law: a report of the FFP/AMLC Investigating Team to Luzon, Visayas and Mindanao, 1979 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Cuba's Position, 1980 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Third World Coalition: Questions and Answers, c. 1980 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Popular Education-Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO), 1997-2000 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Rank and File Committee and Press, 1978-2004 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Katipunan ng mga Demokratikong Pilipino (KDP) 10th Anniversary, 1983 (Box-folder 13/10)
    - The Course of Empire, 1992 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Press and Email List, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Ang Katipunan Workshop, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - The United Front Against War and Fascism, 1935 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - My Last Farewell, Undated (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Political Detainees in the Philippines, 1976 (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Political Prisoners in the Philippines, 1975 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Trades Disputes and Communist Industrial Policy 1920-1923, Part 1 of 2, 1977 (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Trades Disputes and Communist Industrial Policy 1920-1923, Part 2 of 2, 1977 (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Party Building Study, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Basics of Socialism, 1977 (Box-folder 13/21)
    - The Social Structure of San Francisco Chinatown 1848-1906, 1978 (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Free, Enslaved and Indentured Workers in Nineteenth Century California: The Case of Chinese Prostitution, 1978 (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Line of March Discussion Guides and notes, 1980 (Box-folder 13/24)
    - On the Roots of Revisionism, 1979 (Box-folder 13/25)
    - Carlos Bulosan Memorial Exhibit Application, Part 1 of 2, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 13/26)
    - Carlos Bulosan Memorial Exhibit Application, Part 2 of 2, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 13/27)
    - Filipino Activist History Articles, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 13/28)
    - Carlos Bulosan Memorial and Press, Part 1 of 2, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 13/29)
    - Carlos Bulosan Memorial and Press, Part 2 of 2, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 13/30)
    - The Estates of Silme Domingo and Gene Viernes v. Ferdinand Marcos, et al., Newspaper clippings, Part 1 0f 3, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - The Estates of Silme Domingo and Gene Viernes v. Ferdinand Marcos, et al., Newspaper clippings, Part 2 0f 3, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - The Estates of Silme Domingo and Gene Viernes v. Ferdinand Marcos, et al., Newspaper clippings, Part 3 of 3, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 14/3)